# **Ambarish Essetty**

Pune, Maharashtra, India



linkedin.com/in/ambarishessetty



e.ambarishkumar@gmail.com



9337928459

# Summary

Hi, beautiful people, I am Ambarish Essetty who started earning his first gig as a Freelance photographer and now learning as well as creating all forms of content like blogs, videos, infographics, and lots more.

Currently, I blog about my all-time favorite sport, Cricket @ 108cricket.com. Also, I create and optimize content for my clients such as blogs, videos, and social media content.

In the past one year, I have learned one thing, there is only one cheat code to success on the web and that is "High-Quality Content" and that is what I provide to my clients. I work as an SEO Consultant, Digital Marketer, Content Writer, Social Media Manager, Photographer for various businesses and startups.

## **Experience**



### Digital Marketer | Content Creator

108cricket.com

Apr 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months +)

- -After watching several videos and reading 100s of blogs online, I was convinced that I had to practically implement what I learn, otherwise, I cannot grow and that's where I started working on my blog.
- -108cricket.com is the place where I learned everything I know about Digital Marketing and SEO.
- -So, if you are a cricket freak, you should definitely have a look at my content!

### **SEO Specialist**

### Lifetime SOLUTIONS

May 2020 - Present (2 months +)

- LifeTime Solutions is a financial advisory firm, which provides Life Insurance, Health Insurance, and lots more. My main works for the company is to optimize its site for SEO and create content that people love.
- Currently, I am working as a SEO Specialist and working with the content writing team to create the best possible content for the site.

### Digital Marketer

Shree Om Digital Photo Lab

Mar 2020 - Present (4 months +)

- Shree Om Digital Photo Lab is a local business in Bhubaneswar dealing with everything related to Cameras and Photography and they wanted to build their presence online from scratch!
- So, I am working on creating a social media presence for them to focus on their target audience as well as building a website for them which they can use for product listings and providing the latest updates.
- I am currently working as a Full-time Digital marketer for them.

# **Education**



# Symbiosis College of Arts & Commerce

Bachelor of Commerce - BCom, Business/Commerce, General 2019 - 2022

# **Licenses & Certifications**



SEO Fundamentals - SEMrush

5e75e679fd947d2095a368de



**G** Digital Marketing Course - Google

4F4 MY4 5MU

# **Skills**

Digital Marketing • Search Engine Optimization (SEO) • Photography • Blogging • Content Writing • Social Media • WordPress • Adobe Lightroom • Hootsuite